<air:AirFareRulesRsp TraceId="Fly-Far-Tech" TransactionId="6DE64B680A0EE1115FD2D8A5C6B13AC4" ResponseTime="2585" xmlns:air="http://www.travelport.com/schema/air_v52_0">
  <air:FareRule FareInfoRef="KvABdBKDuDKAI4LgRKAAAA==" ProviderCode="ACH" SupplierCode="6E">
    <air:FareRuleLong Category="1000" Type="RULE">Terms and Conditions IndiGo Fares Terms &amp; Conditions

Regular / Promo - One Way retail

Baggage Conditions
Check-in Baggage Allowance: 15 kg for Domestic sectors and 20 kg for International Sectors except 30 Kg for Kuwait, Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Muscat, Damam, Sharjah, Doha, Istanbul and Codeshare destinations; and 25 kg for Jeddah + 5L Zamzam water (only for flights from Jeddah to India)
Hand Baggage Allowance: 7 Kg on IndiGo Operations and 8 Kg on 6E-TK Codeshares. (Including ladies bag and laptop bag.)

Change Fee / Cancel Fee	
Domestic - Respective Change / cancellation charges (click the link below) or 100% of airfare charge (whichever is lower) per passenger per segment will be levied if changed/cancelled at least 3 hrs before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 3 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with Change/Cancellation fees.

International - Respective Change / cancellation charges (click the link below) or 100% of airfare charge (whichever is lower) per passenger per segment will be levied if changed/cancelled at least 4hrs before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 4 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with change fees.

Click here for Change / Cancellation charges:  


Super 6E Fare - The âЂœSuper 6EâЂť fare will include an extra 5kg baggage allowance, free seat selection including XL seat, meal / snack combo, and reduced change and cancellation fee, as well as no convenience fee.
       
        Baggage Conditions
       Check-in Baggage Allowance: An extra 5KG baggage allowance on regular baggage allowance.
       Hand Baggage Allowance:  7 Kg. (including ladies bag and laptop bag.)


Change Fee 
Domestic: No Date Change Fee If changed 4 Days and Above left for departure. Change fee of INR 249 (Per Passenger per sector) will be applicable if changed within 0-3 days from the departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 3 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with change fees.
      
International: No date change fee if changed 4(four) days prior to date of departure and INR 649 per passenger for international sector within 3 (three) days from the date of departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 4 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with change fees.
      

Cancellation Fee 
      
Cancellation fee of only INR 999 per passenger for domestic sector and INR 1999 per passenger for international sector.

If changed/cancelled at least 4hrs before the scheduled departure for International sectors and at least 3hrs before the scheduled departure for Domestic sectors. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 4 hrs (International) and 3hrs (Domestic) from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with change fees. 

                                                                                                                                                                                     Click here for Change / Cancellation charges: 

Return Fare - Applicable for Round-Trip journey

Baggage Conditions
Check-in Baggage Allowance: 15 kg for Domestic sectors and 20 kg for International Sectors except 30 Kg for Kuwait, Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Muscat, Damam, Sharjah, Doha, Istanbul and Codeshare destinations; and 25 kg for Jeddah + 5L Zamzam water (only for flights from Jeddah to India)
Hand Baggage Allowance:  7 Kg on IndiGo Operations and 8 Kg on 6E-TK Codeshares. (Including ladies bag and laptop bag.)

Change Fee / Cancel Fee	
Domestic - Respective Change / cancellation charges (click the link below) or 100% of airfare charge (whichever is lower) per passenger per segment will be levied if changed/cancelled at least 3 hrs before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 3 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with Change/Cancellation fees.

International - Respective Change / cancellation charges (click the link below) or 100% of airfare charge (whichever is lower) per passenger per segment will be levied if changed/cancelled at least 4hrs before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 4 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with change fees. 

Click here for Change / Cancellation charges:  


Family Fare - Applicable on a minimum of 4 pax booked on the same PNR

Baggage Conditions
Check-in Baggage Allowance: 15 kg for Domestic sectors and 20 kg for International Sectors except 30 Kg for Kuwait, Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Muscat, Damam, Sharjah, Doha, Istanbul and Codeshare destinations; and 25 kg for Jeddah + 5L Zamzam water (only for flights from Jeddah to India)
Hand Baggage Allowance:  7 Kg. (including ladies bag and laptop bag.)

Change Fee / Cancel Fee	
Domestic - Respective Change / cancellation charges (click the link below) or 100% of airfare charge (whichever is lower) per passenger per segment will be levied if changed/cancelled at least 3 hrs before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 3 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with Change fees.

International - Respective Change / cancellation charges (click the link below) or 100% of airfare charge (whichever is lower) per passenger per segment will be levied if changed/cancelled at least 4hrs before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 4 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with change fees. 

Click here for Change / Cancellation charges:  


Flexi Fare - Low change and cancelation fee for domestic and international sectors. Fare difference applies.

Baggage Conditions
Check-in Baggage Allowance: 15 kg for Domestic sectors and 20 kg for International Sectors except 30 Kg for Kuwait, Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Muscat, Damam, Sharjah, Doha, Istanbul and Codeshare destinations; and 25 kg for Jeddah + 5L Zamzam water (only for flights from Jeddah to India)
Hand Baggage Allowance:  7 Kg. (including ladies bag and laptop bag.)


Change Fee 
Domestic : INR 299 If changed 4 Days and Above left for departure. Change fee of INR 999 (Per Passenger per sector)will be levied if changed within 0-3 days from the departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 3 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with Change fees.
International: INR 399, if changed at least 4 Days and Above left for departure. Change fee of INR 1999 (Per Passenger per sector)will be levied if changed within 0-3 days from the departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 4 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with change fees.

Cancellation Fee 
Domestic: The cancellation fee will be INR 1999 for cancellation 4 Days and Above left for departure. Cancellation fee up to INR 2999 (Per Passenger per sector) will be levied if cancelled within 0-3 days from the departure.No-show charges will be levied if Booking cancellation is made, less than 3 hours prior to the scheduled departure time.
International: The cancellation fee will be INR 3999 for cancellation 4 Days and Above left for departure. Cancellation fee up to INR 7499 (Per Passenger per sector) will be levied if cancelled within 0-3 days from the departure.No-show charges will be levied if Booking cancellation is made, less than 4 hours prior to the scheduled departure time.


Click here for Change / Cancellation charges:  



SME Fare - WeâЂ™ve got a deal thatâЂ™ll give our travel partners an edge. Unlock a discounted seat* along with lower change and cancellation fee, when you book for business travellers with SME fares. *T&amp;C apply.


Baggage Conditions
Check-in Baggage Allowance: 15 kg for Domestic sectors and 20 kg for International Sectors except 30 Kg for Kuwait, Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Muscat, Damam, Sharjah, Doha, Istanbul and Codeshare destinations; and 25 kg for Jeddah + 5L Zamzam water (only for flights from Jeddah to India)
Hand Baggage Allowance:  7 Kg. (including ladies bag and laptop bag.)

Change Fee 
Domestic Travel : For travel within India, a Change Fee of INR 449 will be charged if change is made to a Booking at least 3 hours before the scheduled departure time. For clarity, no-show charges will be levied if change to a Booking is made within 3 hours prior to the scheduled departure time.
International Travel : For travel to/from an international destination, a Change Fee of INR 999 will be charged if change is made to a Booking at least 4 hours before the scheduled departure time. For clarity, no-show charges will be levied if change to a Booking is made within 4 hours prior to the scheduled departure time.

Cancel Fee	
Domestic Travel : The cancellation fee will be INR 499 per passenger per flight for cancellation if cancelled beyond 24 Hrs prior to departure. Cancellation fee up to INR 1499 (Per Passenger per sector) will be levied if cancelled within 3-24 hours from the departure.No-show charges will be levied if Booking cancellation is made, less than 3 hours prior to the scheduled departure time.
International Travel : The cancellation fee will be INR 999 for cancellation if cancelled beyond 24 Hrs prior to departure. Cancellation fee up to INR 2499 (Per Passenger per sector) will be levied if cancelled within 3-24 Hours from the departure.No-show charges will be levied if Booking cancellation is made, less than 4 hours prior to the scheduled departure time.


Click here for Change / Cancellation charges: 


Lite fare - Applicable for travel without a check-in baggage. Applicable for travel beyond 15 days from the booking date on Domestic and same day on International travel. For a multi-leg/return journey, Lite Fare will be available only if it is available and selected on each of the individual legs.

Baggage Conditions
Check-in Baggage Allowance: No check-in baggage allowed.

Hand Baggage Allowance:  7 Kg. (including ladies bag and laptop bag.)

Change Fee / Cancel Fee	
Domestic - Respective Change / cancellation charges (click the link below) or 100% of airfare charge (whichever is lower) per passenger per segment will be levied if changed/cancelled at least 3 hrs before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 3 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with Change/Cancellation fees.

International - Respective Change / cancellation charges (click the link below) or 100% of airfare charge (whichever is lower) per passenger per segment will be levied if changed/cancelled at least 4hrs before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed/cancelled within 4 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable along with change fees.

Click here for Change / Cancellation charges:  


Corporate / Coupon Fare - Available for contracted Corporate Customers only. Allows unlimited flexibility to change / cancel, extra hand-baggage allowance, complimentary seat and meal (1 food item &amp; 1 beverage). 

Baggage Conditions:
Check-in Baggage Allowance: 15 kg for Domestic sectors and 20 kg for International Sectors except 30 Kg for Kuwait, Abu Dhabi, Dubai, Muscat, Damam, Sharjah, Doha, Istanbul and Codeshare destinations; and 25 kg for Jeddah + 5L Zamzam water (only for flights from Jeddah to India)
Hand Baggage Allowance: 10 Kg. (including ladies bag and laptop bag.)

Change Fee:
Domestic India : No Change Fee: if changed at least 3 hr before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed within 3 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable.
International: No Change Fee: if changed at least 4 hr before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if changed within 4 hrs from scheduled departure. Difference of fare will be applicable.

Cancellation Fee:
Domestic India : No Cancellation Fee: if cancelled at least 3 hr before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if cancelled within 3 hrs from scheduled departure.     
International : No Cancellation Fee: if changed at least 4 hrs before the scheduled departure. No-show charges will be levied if cancelled within 4 hrs from scheduled departure. 
IndiGo Exit Row Seat Rules Seating on all exit rows is subject to the following criteria: 
IndiGo International Connections Check-in Baggage Rules International Connections Check-in baggage option is applicable only for passengers connecting to / from on any International flight within 24 hours of their IndiGo domestic flight. If passenger selects this option then they will be asked to show Boarding pass or valid ticket of international travel at the airport, failing which IndiGo is authorized to charge them excess baggage as per applicable rates at the airport.</air:FareRuleLong>
  </air:FareRule>
</air:AirFareRulesRsp>